# Mike Dreiling

## 2635 Cardinal Drive, Missoula, MT | 406 531 0527 | mdarts@gmail.com

# **Professional Profile**

Hello, My name is Mike Dreiling. I am a graphic designer and developer with over 10 years experience building campaigns for companies in Missoula, Montana. After completing The Montana Code School curriculum and focusing on full stack development I am now in search of an engaging and challenging position with a software development company where I can learn and grow.

# Work Experience

# Lead Graphic Designer & Marketing Coordinator,

2007 - Present

## AlphaGraphics Missoula, Missoula, MT

- Lead and execute all jobs involving creative design, from conception to completion.
- Regularly meet with clients to establish relationships and become acquainted with various brands throughout the market.
- Assist Marketing Manager with creative strategy and execution of all internal marketing campaigns.
- Management and administration of all client order fulfillment websites.
- Produce a variety of print and web material such as catalogs, brochures, business cards, flyers, magazines, ebooks, websites etc...
- Manage and scrutinize over quality, color, and brand consistency in every project.
- Administer and manage AlphaGraphics public-facing website.
- Design and administer client websites using Wordpress platform, HTML and CSS
- Communicate with vendors to establish and properly build various dies and appropriate file types for projects created off-site

#### Graphic Designer,

2007 - 2007

#### Simmons Media, Missoula, MT

- · Produce print design for various Missoula radio stations
- Consult directly with sales representatives and marketing manager to conceptualize new material
- Produce designs for online use and promotional products

## Graphic / Web designer,

2005 - 2006

#### Locomedia Design, Missoula, MT

- Design identity packages for a variety of radio stations located in Sheridan, WY
- Design and implement animated Flash banners and entire Flash web sites

## **Education**

# BA in Media Arts, Associates in Graphic Design

2001 - 2005

#### University of Montana and Seattle Art Institute

Graphic design, website design, animation, and illustration

#### **Development Certification**

2017

#### Montana Code School

Focus on full stack development, usability, agile methodologies, and cutting edge development practices using the MERN stack